Marcel Alexandru Nitan











Email: nitan.marcel@gmail.com
Web: https://github.com/nitanmarcel/

About



Hello! My name is Marcel Alexandru Nitan, I am 22 years old and I am from Suceava, Romania. I studied automotive electronics at Alexandru Ioan Cuza High School, and I finished 12th grade but failed to get the baccalaureate.

I am calm, attentive, and I am always ready to learn new things. I adapt easily to the requirements of the job and I am a person who believes in the expansion of knowledge and experience.

Some of my hobbies are computers and programming. Currently, I know 2 programming languages: Python with 3 years experience and C # with 6 months experience.

Education

Alexandru Ioan Cuza

Automotive Electronics 2013 - 2017

Experience

AngelTrans

Cargo Handler May 2019 - Iul 2019

First Step Consulting

Sales Agent d2d lul 2019 - Oct 2019

Marco Spoleto

Help Chef

Nov 2019 - la 2020

Marcel Alexandru Nitan - nitan.marcel@gmail.com - References available on request.